<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<forms>
	<form>
		<no>0</no>
		<category>Select Category</category>
		<desc>Need Game Master support? Visit our &lt;a href="http://na.aiononline.com/services/support-services"&gt;support site&lt;/a&gt; and let us help.</desc>
		<faq>Petition_selection.xml</faq>
	</form>
	<form>
		<no>1</no>
		<category>Stuck Character</category>
		<desc>Your character is: stuck at a location while moving; repeatedly pulled back to the same coordinates; or unable to log in. First, please check the help information here. If you cannot find the solution, please visit our website.</desc>
		<title>Title</title>
		<content>Text</content>
		<options>
			<option>
				<name>Coords(/loc)</name>
				<length>30</length>
				<required>TRUE</required>
			</option>
		</options>
		<faq>Petition_Move.xml</faq>
	</form>
	<form>
		<no>2</no>
		<category>Restore Character</category>
		<desc>When a character is killed due to a bug or system error, suffering a loss of XP or items, GMs may restore the character based on an examination of in-game logs. Restoration can only take place when full records of the bug exist.</desc>
		<title>Title</title>
		<content>Text</content>
		<options>
			<option>
				<name>Category</name>
				<length>10</length>
				<required>TRUE</required>
			</option>
		</options>
		<faq>Petition_restore.xml</faq>
	</form>
	<form>
		<no>3</no>
		<category>Reporting a Bug</category>
		<desc>If you encounter an error while playing, please report it in detail including the [bug's effect] and the [steps to reproduce] it. Active reporting of even small bugs helps us improve the quality of Aion. Responses to bug-related tickets may be delayed at times as they require confirmation and testing. We appreciate both your assistance and your patience.</desc>
		<title>Title</title>
		<content>Text</content>
		<options>
			<option>
				<name>Time Occurred</name>
				<length>15</length>
				<required>TRUE</required>
			</option>
			<option>
				<name>Zone and Coords</name>
				<length>10</length>
				<required>TRUE</required>
			</option>
			<option>
				<name>How to Replicate</name>
				<length>10</length>
				<required>FALSE</required>
			</option>
		</options>
		<faq>Petition_bug.xml</faq>
	</form>
	<form>
		<no>4</no>
		<category>Quests</category>
		<desc>Find tips for completing a quest, along with information about rewards, from the Aion community forums and the Game Guide. If you encounter a bug or error, please visit our support site for more help.</desc>
		<title>Title</title>
		<content>Text</content>
		<options>
			<option>
				<name>Quest Title</name>
				<length>30</length>
				<required>TRUE</required>
			</option>
		</options>
		<faq>Petition_Quest.xml</faq>
	</form>
	<form>
		<no>5</no>
		<category>Reporting Unacceptable Behavior</category>
		<desc>If you come across an incident that is in violation of the rules, i.e. a fraudulent activity, verbal insults, use of other inappropriate language, etc., please go to our support website and let us know.</desc>
		<title>Title</title>
		<content>Text</content>
		<options>
			<option>
				<name>Time Occurred</name>
				<length>15</length>
				<required>TRUE</required>
			</option>
			<option>
				<name>Character Name</name>
				<length>10</length>
				<required>TRUE</required>
			</option>
			<option>
				<name>Category</name>
				<length>10</length>
				<required>TRUE</required>
			</option>
		</options>
		<faq>Petition_declarationl.xml</faq>
	</form>
	<form>
		<no>6</no>
		<category>Suggestions</category>
		<desc>We review all submitted suggestions, but are unable to respond to each one except to acknowledge receipt of the petition. Where appropriate, we will respond with the outcome of suggestions on the Aion website. We value all suggestions from our customers and appreciate your patience as we work to improve Aion.</desc>
		<title>Title</title>
		<content>Text</content>
		<options>
			<option>
				<name>Category</name>
				<length>15</length>
				<required>TRUE</required>
			</option>
		</options>
		<faq>Petition_proposal.xml</faq>
	</form>
	<form>
		<no>255</no>
		<category>Inquiries about the Game</category>
		<desc>If you don't find the information you're looking for in the in-game help and information, other inquiries about the game can be submitted through the support website, or on the forums.</desc>
		<title>Title</title>
		<content>Text</content>
		<options>
			<option>
				<name>Petition Category</name>
				<length>15</length>
				<required>FALSE</required>
			</option>
		</options>
		<faq>Petition_game.xml</faq>
	</form>
</forms>