<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<forms>
	<form>
		<no>0</no>
		<category>Choose Category</category>
		<desc>Aion has prepared a full and comprehensive FAQ divided into several categories to assist our customers to enjoy a smooth gaming experience. Please check the FAQ categories, and if you don't find the information you're looking for, submit a petition for assistance.</desc>
		<faq>Petition_selection.xml</faq>
	</form>
	<form>
		<no>1</no>
		<category>Character Stuck</category>
		<desc>This refers to a situation in which a character is stuck at a location while moving, is repeatedly pulled back to the same coordinates, or cannot log in. First, please check the following FAQ. If you cannot find the solution there, please click [Petition] to submit a petition.</desc>
		<title>Title</title>
		<content>Text</content>
		<options>
			<option>
				<name>Coordinates(/Location)</name>
				<length>30</length>
				<required>TRUE</required>
			</option>
		</options>
		<faq>Petition_Move.xml</faq>
	</form>
	<form>
		<no>3</no>
		<category>Reporting a Bug</category>
		<desc>If you encounter an error while playing, please report it in detail including the [bug's effect] and the [steps to reproduce] it. Active reporting of even small bugs helps us improve the quality of Aion. Responses to bug-related petitions may be delayed at times as they require confirmation and testing. We appreciate both your assistance and your patience.</desc>
		<title>Title</title>
		<content>Text</content>
		<options>
			<option>
				<name>Time of Occurrence</name>
				<length>15</length>
				<required>TRUE</required>
			</option>
			<option>
				<name>Region and Coordinates</name>
				<length>10</length>
				<required>TRUE</required>
			</option>
			<option>
				<name>Revival</name>
				<length>10</length>
				<required>FALSE</required>
			</option>
		</options>
		<faq>Petition_bug.xml</faq>
	</form>
	<form>
		<no>4</no>
		<category>Quest Related</category>
		<desc>You can obtain information about solving a quest, tips, and rewards for completing the quest from player community sites. You can get more help from the FAQ below, and also consulting the [Aion Answers] and [Power Wiki]. If you encounter game errors, please submit a petition with the details (title of quest, name of NPC, description of the situation) and we will get back to you when we have identified the problem.</desc>
		<title>Title</title>
		<content>Text</content>
		<options>
			<option>
				<name>Quest Name</name>
				<length>30</length>
				<required>TRUE</required>
			</option>
		</options>
		<faq>Petition_Quest.xml</faq>
	</form>
	<form>
		<no>5</no>
		<category>Reporting Unacceptable Behavior</category>
		<desc>If you come across an incident that is in violation of the rules, i.e. a fraudulent activity, verbal insults, use of other inappropriate language, etc., please submit a petition with the relevant details. We will investigate the incident and respond when we have resolved the problem.</desc>
		<title>Title</title>
		<content>Text</content>
		<options>
			<option>
				<name>Time of Occurrence</name>
				<length>15</length>
				<required>TRUE</required>
			</option>
			<option>
				<name>Target Character</name>
				<length>10</length>
				<required>TRUE</required>
			</option>
			<option>
				<name>Report Category</name>
				<length>10</length>
				<required>TRUE</required>
			</option>
		</options>
		<faq>Petition_declarationl.xml</faq>
	</form>
	<form>
		<no>6</no>
		<category>Suggestions</category>
		<desc>We review all submitted suggestions, but are unable to respond to each one except to acknowledge receipt of the petition. Where appropriate, we will respond with the outcome of suggestions on the Aion website. We value all suggestions from our customers and appreciate your patience as we work to improve Aion.</desc>
		<title>Title</title>
		<content>Text</content>
		<options>
			<option>
				<name>Suggestion Category</name>
				<length>15</length>
				<required>TRUE</required>
			</option>
		</options>
		<faq>Petition_proposal.xml</faq>
	</form>
	<form>
		<no>255</no>
		<category>Inquiry about the Game</category>
		<desc>The in-game 1:1 petition service provides a direct channel to the Aion production team, allowing players to submit error reports and suggestions for improving Aion. You can obtain basic game information and more from the FAQ below, and by using [Aion Answers] and [Power Wiki]. 1:1 petitions received in-game may be used for updating the FAQ.</desc>
		<title>Title</title>
		<content>Text</content>
		<options>
			<option>
				<name>Petition Category</name>
				<length>15</length>
				<required>FALSE</required>
			</option>
		</options>
		<faq>Petition_game.xml</faq>
	</form>
</forms>