<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<category>
	<faq>
		<question>Death Penalty and Soul Healing</question>
		<answer>Upon dying, a character receives penalties, including a loss of XP and death after effects (debuff). A Soul Healer can treat the death aftereffects, and also recover some of the lost XP. If you are not treated by a Soul Healer, the duration of the debuff accumulates, and affects you later. if you don't receive treatment after death, the fee becomes higher when you receive Soul Healing later (characters under level 5 are not affected by death penalties).</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Obelisks</question>
		<answer>You can bind to an [%dic:STR_DIC_ELA16] for the resurrection and return of your character. If you click an Obelisk (located in each region), and pay the fee to bind, your character will be returned to that Obelisk after death.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Rifts</question>
		<answer>A [%dic:STR_DIC_E_directportal] is a corridor which leads to the territory of the opposing race. Rifts appear in the [%dic:STR_DIC_E_LF2_name] and [%dic:STR_DIC_E_LF3_name] regions of Elysea and the [%dic:STR_DIC_E_DF2_name] and [%dic:STR_DIC_E_DF3_name] regions of Asmodae at certain times only. You are returned to your own territory upon death or use of the Return skill.  You can also return through a Rift that opens in enemy territory.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Learning your first Skill</question>
		<answer>To learn a skill, you have to complete the New Skill quest when your character reaches level 3. After completing this quest, you can buy Skill Manuals to learn new skills. You can buy the Skill Manuals from class-specific Instructors in the starting village or Trainers in the city. To learn the skills, double-click the manuals you have purchased. Some Skill Manuals are obtained from hunting monsters, or as rewards for completing quests.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Learning New Skills and Increasing Skill Levels</question>
		<answer>The level of the skills that a character has learned increases when the character's level increases. You can learn a new skill by purchasing a Skill Manual from a Trainer or Master of each class. Trainers and Masters for each class are found in the villages of [%dic:STR_DIC_E_LF1_name] and [%dic:STR_DIC_E_DF1_name] region, and also in [%dic:STR_DIC_ELA07], [%dic:STR_DIC_ELA08], the [%dic:STR_DIC_W_DC2], and the [%dic:STR_DIC_W_LC2].</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Chain Skills</question>
		<answer>A Chain Skill executes several skills one after the other. Using the Activation Skill initiates the remainder of the Chain Skill. For example, using Soul Slash after Quick Slash inflicts additional damage on the target, and there is also a chance of stunning the target. To view Chain Skill information, click the Chain Skill Info button on the top right of the Skill window (default &lt;K&gt; key). The Skills Info window shows the Chain Skills you can use right now, and also the Chain Skills you will be able to use in the future.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>DP Skills</question>
		<answer>DP is an abbreviation for Divine Power. Divine Power accumulates slowly over time when [%dic:STR_DIC_ELA09]s hunt monsters. You can use powerful skills that require DP when the accumulated DP reaches a certain level. DP is also used in certain aspects of Crafting. DP is accumulated very slowly through combat, and disappears in a specific amount of time after you exit the game.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Classes that Require Skill Consumables</question>
		<answer>Assassins, Rangers, and Spiritmasters require class supplies to use certain skills. To see information on the necessary class supplies, go to  Skill (Default &lt;K&gt; key) Info. You can purchase class supplies from the job supplies merchants in [%dic:STR_DIC_ELA07] and [%dic:STR_DIC_ELA08], and also from the general goods merchants in each fortress and village.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Stigma Skills and Stigma Shards</question>
		<answer>A Stigma is a stone that contains the power and memory of deceased [%dic:STR_DIC_ELA09]s. You can use a Stigma to enhance your character's attributes or mitigate your vulnerabilities. You can begin using Stigmas once you reach level 20 and complete the related quest. To equip a Stigma and use its abilities, you must take the Stigma and some Stigma Shards to a Stigma Master.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Power Shards</question>
		<answer>A Power Shard is an item that temporarily increases the attack power of the weapon a character is carrying. You can get them from general goods merchants or by hunting monsters. To equip a Power Shard, double-clicking the Power Shard in your Inventory. To use the equipped Power Shard, press the &lt;B&gt; key to activate it. When you are not using the weapon, press the &lt;B&gt; key again to deactivate it.  Equipped and activated Power Shards are consumed when the weapon is used in combat.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Cubes</question>
		<answer>A [%dic:STR_DIC_ELA17] is the space in which a character carries items. There is a limit on the number of slots in a Cube, but you can increase the number of slots by expanding the Cube. To expand a cube, pay a fee to a Cube Craftsman, or carry out special quests.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Dyes</question>
		<answer>You can change the color of an item by using a dye. Obtain dyes by purchasing them from NPC stores in a city, or through completing quests or hunting. To use, double-click the dye, then click the item to dye.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Adjusting the Interface</question>
		<answer>The Game Options tab of the Options window (&lt;O&gt; key)  will let you choose between two User Interface (UI) styles. The default Aion Style shows your character information heads-up display (HUD) at the bottom of the screen. You can change to a HUD Top Style, in the dropdown options of the UI Style. To apply the new UI style press the Apply button.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Extended Quickbars</question>
		<answer>You can use skills or items more easily by placing them on the Quickbars. Initially only one Quickbar is displayed on the bottom of the game screen. You can add up to three more Quickbars. To expand the Quickbars, press the &lt;O&gt; key, then select Options from the System Menu. On the User Interface in the Game Preferences tab of the Options window, check the Display Extended Quickbar check boxes in order and press the Apply button.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>NPCs that cannot be found with Find Location</question>
		<answer>There are some NPCs that cannot be located by using the Find Location function/s
			. Remember to check inside buildings or caves when looking for hard-to-find NPCs.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Changing Chat Mode</question>
		<answer>To designate which window you want to enter chat text into, use the following commands in front of your dialog. /s = General Chat, /g = Group Chat, /a = Alliance Chat, /l = Legion Chat, /league = League Chat, /y = Shout, /w character name = Whisper.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Linking Items in the Chat Window</question>
		<answer>To link an item in the Chat window, activate the Chat window, then Ctrl-Right-Click the item you want to link to.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Brokers</question>
		<answer>Brokers help players trade with one another, like the Private Store System. Unlike the Private Store system, Brokers charge a fee to list your items. You can also search and buy items from other characters. To list an item for sale, drag the item from your [%dic:STR_DIC_ELA17] to the Broker window, and enter the desired price.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Splitting Stacks of Items</question>
		<answer>To move part of a stack of items, Shift-Right-Click to open a quantity window, then enter the desired quantity into the field.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Item Enchantment</question>
		<answer>Item Enchantment improves the existing abilities of an item using enchanting materials. You can obtain the materials needed for enchanting by extracting them from other items using Extraction Tools.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Godstones</question>
		<answer>Godstones allow a weapon to inflict additional damage or cause other effects. To socket a Godstone, talk to a Godstone Socketer in Sanctum or Pandaemonium, then place the weapon and Godstone in the Godstone Socket window and pay the fee. You can get Godstones from hunting monsters or as rewards for completing quests.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Manastones</question>
		<answer>Manastones confer additional abilities on an item. You can obtain Manastones by hunting monsters, or as rewards for completing quests. To socket a Manastone, double-click the Manastone, then click on an item with an available Manastone socket. if the socketing is not successful, the Manastone is destroyed. Moreover, when you fail to socket an additional Manastone to an item that already has other Manastone(s) socketed, the existing Manastone(s) are also destroyed.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Modifying Item Appearance</question>
		<answer>Appearance modification changes the appearance of an item while maintaining the item's existing attributes. To modify the appearance of an item, visit the Appearance Modifier in Sanctum or Pandaemonium. You'll need the item whose appearance you want to change, and an item to take the appearance from. The items must be of the same type.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Title</question>
		<answer>A Title is a modifier for your character's name that also boosts your character's attributes. You can obtain Titles by completing specific quests, or from hunting specific monsters. View and change Titles from the Title tab of the Profile window. As each Title gives different bonuses, choose the most suitable Title for your class or situation.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Legions</question>
		<answer>Legions are communities similar to guilds or blood alliances in other games. They are organizations created by like-minded players to socialize with one another, and/or to battle enemies and complete quests. The number of members allowed in a Legion varies according to its Legion level. To increase a Legion's level, certain conditions must be met. To found or disband a Legion, visit the Legion founding manager in the Legion administration office in Sanctum or Pandaemonium.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Flight System</question>
		<answer>You gain the ability to fly when you Ascend from a Human to a [%dic:STR_DIC_ELA09]. However, flying is only possible in places filled with the power of Aether, such as fortresses that have fragments of Aion's Tower in them. You can fight or gather while flying, and you can extract [%dic:STR_DIC_I_od_d_n_c_20a]s from Aether fragments floating in the sky.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Glide System</question>
		<answer>Gliding is the action of spreading your wings and riding air currents to descend slowly from high places. You can glide anywhere, regardless of flight restrictions, once you have completed the Ascension quest, but unlike flying you cannot fight or use skills or items while gliding. When you leap down from a high place and press &lt;Space Bar&gt; while jumping (when the Flying Gauge is above 0) you will glide. You can only change directions to left or right or descend when gliding, and pressing &lt;Space Bar&gt; once more ends the glide.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Gathering</question>
		<answer>The Gathering skill is automatically known when a character is created. Higher levels in this skill allow you to gather more valuable items. You can only gather on the ground before Ascension, but after Ascension you can also gather in the air. Items obtained from gathering are used for Crafting.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Crafting</question>
		<answer>You can learn crafting by paying a Crafting Master in the city to teach you. When you have learned a crafting skill, you can begin making items in the workshops in Sanctum or Pandaemonium. The available crafting skills include weaponsmithing, armorsmithing, tailoring, cooking, alchemy, and handicrafting.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Warehouses</question>
		<answer>Private Warehouses, Account Warehouses, and Legion Warehouses are located in the fortresses of each region, and in cities. Private Warehouses can only be used by one character. Account Warehouses can be shared by all characters on the same account. Legion Warehouses can only be used by members of that Legion.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Mail</question>
		<answer>You can send both letters and items to other characters by using the mailbox. To check mail you have received or send mail to other characters, click a mailbox located in a city, village, or fortress. The two types of mail available are Normal Mail and Express Mail. Check the mailbox for normal mail. Express mail is delivered directly to the character by a courier.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Find Friends</question>
		<answer>Find Friends allows you to check your friends login status and information, and you can also search for players that meet your conditions who are willing to join a group. Also, by listing a character in the Block tab you can block the character from sending messages to you.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Player Search</question>
		<answer>The Friends List, located in Social window (Default &lt;V&gt; key), displays information on your Friends: their character name, level, class, current location, and login status. You can also keep your own notes there. The Search tab of the Social window allows you to search for characters by name, level, region, level, and/or class. The Search tab can help you form groups with an &lt;Invite to Group&gt; button, and while ungrouped, you can set your gameplay status (Solo / Looking for Group) for display to other players. The Block tab, located in Social window &lt;V&gt; key, allows you to indicate characters from whom you no longer want to receive general, region, group or whisper messages.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Sub-Class Selection</question>
		<answer>Sub-class selection in Aion occurs by completing a particular quest, which is given automatically, and appears on the Quest window when your character reaches level 9. Part of this quest will be choosing between two sub-classes available to your basic character class, allowing your character to become more specialized. Consider this choice carefully, as you cannot change your class once it is chosen.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Blocking</question>
		<answer>If you are receiving unwelcome communications from a specific player, use the Find function in System / Menu / Community. To block a character from sending messages to you, enter the character's name in the Block tab.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Producing Screenshots</question>
		<answer>To capture screenshots in-game, press the PrintScreen key. Screenshots are saved in the Screenshot subfolder inside the Aion game folder.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Chat Window Options</question>
		<answer>By default, Chat tabs are divided into All, Normal, Combat, and Group windows. You can modify them according to your play style by using the tab option in the Chat window. To use Add Tab, Delete Tab, Change Tab Name, and Tab Option, place your mouse on the tab above the Chat window and right-click it.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Game System Preferences</question>
		<answer>To change game system preferences, press the &lt;O&gt; key. Select the System Preferences in the System Menu. The System Preferences window is divided into Game Preferences, Graphic Preferences, Sound Preferences, and Key Settings tabs.</answer>
	</faq>
</category>