<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<category>
	<faq>
		<question>Fraud</question>
		<answer>Fraudulent activities that induce other players to make mistakes will be dealt with according to our terms of service. If you have become a victim of fraud by another player, please report to us with the details in full. We will investigate the report thoroughly, and take appropriate action. Fraudulent items are deleted as a rule, and the terms of service state that those items cannot be returned or restored.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Abusive Language</question>
		<answer>If a player is causing discomfort through the use of inappropriate or abusive language, please report to us with the character's name, the time of the incident, and the details. We will investigate the incident and address the matter as soon as possible according to our terms of service.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Blocking Harassment</question>
		<answer>If you have difficulty playing the game due to another player's harassment, try using the Friend options found at System Menu - Community. You can block a character from sending messages to you by entering the character's name in the Block tab.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Disputes</question>
		<answer>Disputes between players can occur in the game for a variety of reasons. As interactions with other players are one of the game's features, we recommend that players solve their disputes through calm communication. As a rule, the GMs will not intervene in disputes between players to pass judgment on matters other than those specified by the terms of serive. We apologize that we may not be able to provide assistance.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Illegal Programs</question>
		<answer>If, during gameplay, you discover anyone using a program not supported by us, please report it to us with the character's name and details of the incident. We will investigate, and take appropriate action.  We ask for your understanding for any delays that may occur as we as we obtain the evidence of the use of an illegal program and give monitor warning, etc.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Other Unacceptable Player Behavior</question>
		<answer>If a player disrupts the game through means other than fraud or abusive language, please report to us with the character's name and details of the incident. We will investigate the incident and take action if it is confirmed that the player has violated the terms of service.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Ban on Chat</question>
		<answer>Repeated spamming and use of abusive language in the Chat window may lead to a ban on chat in accordance with our terms of service. We thank you for your cooperation with us in maintaining a clean and fun gaming culture.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Character/Account Access Restriction Related Inquiry</question>
		<answer>For general inquiries regarding restricted access to characters or accounts, please use the 1:1 Petition service available on our website.</answer>
	</faq>
	<faq>
		<question>Suggestions on Operating Policy</question>
		<answer>If you have any questions or suggestions t regarding operation policies that may improve gameplay, please use the 1:1 Petition service available on our website rather than the one in-game.</answer>
	</faq>
</category>